<?xml version="1.0"?>
<info xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="https://apps.nextcloud.com/schema/apps/info.xsd">
	<id>signotecsignosignuniversal</id>
	<name>signotec signoSign</name>
	<summary>Sign documents with signotec signoSign</summary>
	<summary lang="de">Dokumente signieren mit signotec signoSign</summary>
	<description><![CDATA[**Sign documents seamlessly — right inside Nextcloud**

Simplify your document workflow by signing PDF documents directly within Nextcloud or by inviting others to sign remotely — no extra tools, logins, or installations required.

*Effortless signing. Smarter workflows. Fully secure.*

## Key Features

- **Local Signing:** Sign PDFs yourself or directly at the Point of Sale (POS).
- **Remote Signing:** Invite others to sign via email.
- **Simple and Easy:** External signatories do not require any account or registration process.
- **Biometric Signatures:** Capture true handwritten signatures via touch, stylus, or signotec signature pads.
- **SMS Authentication:** Verify the signer's identity with secure SMS-based authentication. (optional)
- **Automatic Field Detection:** Predefine search terms to automatically place mandatory or optional signature fields.
- **Automatic Upload:** Once completed, signed documents are uploaded back to Nextcloud via webhook.
- **Personalized Settings:** Your preferred sharing options are remembered per user.
- **Secure & Compliant:** Signatures comply with EU eIDAS and ISO standards for legally valid PDF signing.

**Start today** with a **30-day free trial** – no payment details required and no subscription commitment. Explore all our features completely free!

[Click here to register your trial now](https://universal.signosign.com/signotecAdmintool/free-trial.seam)

## About signotec

For over **25 years**, **signotec** has been a world-leading provider of handwritten biometric signature solutions for signature pads and mobile devices. signotec's technology ensures maximum security, usability, and compliance with EU-eIDAS and ISO regulations — trusted by organizations worldwide for secure digital document workflows.

Get documents signed faster — directly where your work happens.

Visit our website at [www.signotec.com](https://www.signotec.com).]]></description>
	<description lang="de"><![CDATA[**Dokumente nahtlos signieren — direkt in Nextcloud**

Vereinfachen Sie Ihren Dokumenten-Workflow, indem Sie PDF-Dokumente direkt in Nextcloud signieren oder andere zum Signieren einladen – ohne zusätzliche Tools, Logins oder Installationen.

*Müheloses Signieren. Intelligentere Workflows. Vollständig sicher.*

## Funktionen

- **Lokales Signieren:** Signieren Sie PDFs selbst oder direkt am Point of Sale (POS).
- **Fernunterschrift:** Laden Sie andere per E-Mail zum Signieren ein.
- **Einfach und unkompliziert:** Externe Unterzeichner benötigen kein Konto und keine Registrierung.
- **Biometrische Unterschriften:** Erfassen Sie echte handschriftliche Unterschriften per Touch, Stift oder signotec-Signaturpads.
- **SMS-Authentifizierung:** Verifizieren Sie die Identität des Unterzeichners per SMS. (optional)
- **Automatische Felderkennung:** Definieren Sie Suchbegriffe, um Pflicht- oder optionale Signaturfelder automatisch zu platzieren.
- **Automatischer Upload:** Signierte Dokumente werden nach Abschluss automatisch per Webhook in Nextcloud hochgeladen.
- **Personalisierte Einstellungen:** Bevorzugte Freigabeoptionen werden pro Benutzer gespeichert.
- **Sicher & konform:** Unterschriften entsprechen den EU-eIDAS- und ISO-Standards für rechtsgültige PDF-Signaturen.

**Starten Sie noch heute** mit einer **30-tägigen kostenlosen Testversion** – keine Zahlungsdaten erforderlich, keine Abonnementverpflichtung. Entdecken Sie alle Funktionen völlig kostenlos!

[Jetzt kostenlose Testversion registrieren](https://universal.signosign.com/signotecAdmintool/free-trial.seam)

## Über signotec

Seit über **25 Jahren** ist **signotec** weltweit führender Anbieter von handschriftlichen biometrischen Signaturlösungen für Signaturpads und mobile Geräte. Die Technologie von signotec gewährleistet maximale Sicherheit, Benutzerfreundlichkeit und Konformität mit EU-eIDAS- und ISO-Vorschriften – weltweit vertraut für sichere digitale Dokumenten-Workflows.

Lassen Sie Dokumente schneller signieren – direkt dort, wo Ihre Arbeit stattfindet.

Besuchen Sie unsere Website unter [www.signotec.com](https://www.signotec.com).]]></description>
	<version>1.0.0</version>
	<licence>AGPL-3.0-or-later</licence>
	<author mail="integrations@signotec.de" homepage="https://www.signotec.com/">signotec GmbH</author>
	<namespace>SignotecSignoSignUniversal</namespace>
	<category>integration</category>
	<category>office</category>
	<bugs>https://github.com/jro-signotec/nextcloud-signotecsignosignuniversal/issues</bugs>
	<screenshots>
		<screenshot order="1">screenshots/Nextcloud_App_Store_SIGN.png</screenshot>
		<screenshot order="2">screenshots/Nextcloud_App_Store_EDIT.png</screenshot>
		<screenshot order="3">screenshots/Nextcloud_App_Store_SHARE.png</screenshot>
		<screenshot order="4">screenshots/Nextcloud_App_Store_MOBILE.png</screenshot>
		<screenshot order="5">screenshots/Nextcloud_App_Store_Context_Menu.png</screenshot>
		<screenshot order="6">screenshots/Nextcloud_App_Store_Send_Form.png</screenshot>
	</screenshots>
	<dependencies>
		<nextcloud min-version="32" max-version="32" />
	</dependencies>
	<settings>
		<admin>OCA\SignotecSignoSignUniversal\Settings\UniversalAdmin</admin>
		<admin-section>OCA\SignotecSignoSignUniversal\Sections\UniversalAdmin</admin-section>
	</settings>
</info>